this is what your boycott says about you all right let's start with mcdonald's if you boycott
them i'm proud of you okay this is level one this is light work all right because honestly
i can make a better burger on the engine of a car all right if you add starbucks to the list
duh duh how many times are we gonna have to boycott them we boycott them every summer
leave them alone okay my granny makes a better coffee than this and she uses prune juice
all right level two is black friday this is when a lot of companies make their money it's not even
black friday no more it's black november at this point you have enough stuff y'all don't need you
got everything you need you got everything you need you don't need nothing else okay now we're
moving on to level three okay this is a level three boycott we getting the apple right now
yes i have on an apple watch right now do you think i'll be getting another one
no i will not okay not until we get our resources ethically and i just want to say this doesn't
stop at black friday there's no end date for this okay it's time to really think about the way that
we consume because that's where we hold our power baby you have enough jeans you have enough sweaters
you have enough coats you know what keeps me warm liberation and community so comment below and tell
me what you're going to be boycotting so that we can create some cute community up in here and take
our power back
Thank you.